<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML>
    <letter>
        <date> July 26, 1955</date>
        <place>Brussels</place>

        <readers>Dear Peoples</readers>
        <p n="1">We are just about to take off for Copenhagen and are sit- ting around so I will try
            to send this second installment of our trip report. If I remember correctly, the last
            letter came from the boat. We arrived in Cherbourg and got safely on the train to fin
            that it was over 90. We nearly died on the ride to Paris. Very unairconditioned train
            and blazing sun. The first thing we did when we arrived at Le Bristol was fall in cold
            tub. We went out for dinner later and cele- brater with Charles Jubilee. Very tasty! The
            next day Mrs. Behrend hired a car and guide and we drove all over Paris. It is so
            beautiful but so expensive<x rw="?">!</x>
            <faded>$</faded>90 a minute to breath! We did a bit of shopping, had lunch in the Bois
            de Boulougne shopped on the Left Bank, got train tickets and that night went to the
            Casino de Paris. Pretty naked ladies I must say. We were not carried away by it but did
            see it, so that is that.</p>
        <p n="2">The next morning we were up at the crack of dawn and off to Tours. The man and his
            wife who ran the Manior Berheron, where we stayed as a mm ber of the family were
            terribly nice. We arravied in time for lunch and then got in a little car and went
            through some beautiful country to see some of the chateaux. We enjoyed it traemndously.
            You can see where the old French painters get all their inspirations. Lovely rivers, old
            mills and beautiful trees. That night after dinner we went to a nearby chateau,
            Azay-le-Rideau which was illuminated. Just like fairyland. They also had a sort of play
            very cleverly done just done with voices and lighting which told the history of the
            building. We will never forget it.</p>
        <p n="3">Thursday, the Davidsons, our hosts and their little boy and and ourselves went on
            another chateaux trip which was just a grand as the day before. We had a picnic on the
            way and <x rw="tea">day</x> on the way home. Great fun. The only thing that marred the
            trip was another guest who arrived who knew all about everything and told it in the
            loudest of voices. I got in a ter- rible row with him about sports. Everyone was on my
            side but you couldn't get a word in edge wise. Itwas rather funny to look back on but I
            nearly had a nervous breakdown when it was going on.</p>

        <p n="4"> Friday we left Tours at about eleven and got back in Paris for lunch. After the
            lovely meal we changed out on foot to do some shopping.</p>
    </letter>
</XML>
